* [Disney Springs](https://disneyspringshotels.com/disney-springs-things-to-do/ "Things to do at Disney Springs (formerly Dowtown Disney)")

Privacy Policy
==============

This site is owned by the HOTEL PLAZA ASSOCIATION (collectively referred to herein as “DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS”). This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using, or submitting information, to this site.

**Your Consent**

By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**About Children**

This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Websites.

**Active Information Collection**

Like many Websites, this site actively collects information from its visitors both by asking you specific questions and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail and forms. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on collectively referred to herein as “Personal Information”). We will never sell, transfer, or disclose any Personal Information we gather at our Websites to any third parties without your prior consent, except in cases when we believe in good faith that we have a legal obligation to disclose such Personal Information. We never require that this Personal Information be provided in order to gain access to our sites, nor will we require visitors to disclose more Personal Information than is reasonably needed to participate in an activity on our sites. Some areas of this site may require you to submit Personal Information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, tips/pointers, etc.) or to participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes or other promotions). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

**Passive Information Collection**

As you navigate through our Website, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet tags, and navigational data collection.

This site may use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet and is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address is dynamic (changing each time you connect to the Internet), rather than static (unique to a particular user’s computer). We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our site, and administer and improve the site.

A “cookie” is a bit of information that a Website sends to your Web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences.

“Persistent” cookies are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer and stay there unless you delete the cookie. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided (e.g., passwords), helping to determine what areas of the Website visitors find most valuable, and customizing the Website based on your preferences. This site may use persistent cookies.

“Internet tags” (also known as single pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, and 1xbyx1 GIFs) are smaller than cookies and tell the Website server information such as the IP address and browser type related to the visitor’s computer. This site may use Internet tags. Tags have been placed both on online advertisements that bring people to the site and on different pages of the site. These tags indicate how many times a page is opened and which information is consulted. We do not collect or seek personally identifiable information through these tags.

“Navigational data” (“log files,” “server logs,” and “clickstream” data) are used for system management, to improve the content of the site, market research purposes, and to communicate information to visitors. This site may use navigational data.

**Use and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise stated, we may use your information to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes, and for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.

If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We will take reasonable measures to prevent personally identifiable information from being combined with passively collected information, unless you consent otherwise.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information to the DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties, located in the United States and/or any other country, but only to contractors we use to support our business (e.g., fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.

In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not in personally identifiable form.

**Communications To DSRAH**

DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS appreciates hearing from you. However, in your communications with us, please keep in mind that any communication or material you transmit to any of our Websites by electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, recipes, creative suggestions, ideas, concepts, products, marketing or promotional plans or strategies, or the like shall be deemed and shall remain the exclusive property of DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS. You understand and acknowledge that DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS has the resources which may have developed or may in the future develop ideas identical to or similar to your suggestions or comments and that DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS is only willing to consider suggestions and ideas on the terms set forth herein.

Any suggestion, idea, or comment is not submitted in confidence and DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS assumes no obligation, express or implied, by considering it. Without limitation, DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS shall exclusively own all now known or hereafter existing rights to the suggestions, ideas or comments of every kind and nature and DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS shall be entitled to unrestricted use of the suggestions, ideas or comments for any purposes whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, including, but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcasting or posting without any compensation to the provider of the suggestions, ideas or comments.

Sign Up for Special Offers

_Disney Springs®_ Resort Area Hotels

Advantage
=========

#### Transportation

Individual Daily Shuttle Service to Disney Theme Parks during normal operating hours. Reservations required.

#### Exclusive Passport

Enjoy all that _DISNEY SPRINGS®_ has to offer with this [guide and savings booklet](https://goadmi.com/3d-flip-book/disney-springs-passport).

#### _DISNEY SPRINGS®_ LOCATION

130+ establishments - a mix of shops, a collection of menus by award-winning chefs, and exceptional live entertainment just steps away.

#### _Walt Disney World®_ Resort Championship Golf

Book your tee-times up to 90 days in advance!

Insider News
============

[Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party](https://disneyspringshotels.com/mickeys-very-merry-christmas-party/ "Permanent Link to Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party")   Select Nights from November 8 – December 20, Guests can Experience the Holiday Magic at Magic Kingdom® Park Do you still believe in holiday magic? Discover it again as you step into a Yuletide tale full of warm and wonderful traditions during Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party at Magic Kingdom® Park. Join Mickey and… [View Article »](https://disneyspringshotels.com/mickeys-very-merry-christmas-party/)

[DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS THIS FALL](https://disneyspringshotels.com/disney-springs-resort-area-hotels-fall-2024/ "Permanent Link to DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS THIS FALL") UPDATE RATES START AT $96 AT DISNEY SPRINGS® RESORT AREA HOTELS Stay Steps from the Most Magical Place on Earth this Season LAKE BUENA VISTA, Fla. – (Oct. 21, 2024) – Special rates starting at $96 are available to book at Disney Springs Resort Area Hotels for stays through November 23, 2024. Some blackout dates… [View Article »](https://disneyspringshotels.com/disney-springs-resort-area-hotels-fall-2024/)

Let's Connect
=============

Sign Up for Special Offers

    * [Disney Springs](https://disneyspringshotels.com/disney-springs-things-to-do/ "Things to do at Disney Springs (formerly Dowtown Disney)")

As to Disney artwork, logos, and properties:

©Disney ©Disney•Pixar  
©Fox  
©Disney © & TM Lucasfilm Ltd.
